Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- M
  - Mayo, John S., undated; cuid1731 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Mazziota, Daniel, undated; cuid1732 (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Mazzucco, Salvatore, 1975; cuid1733 (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - McCabe, Warren L., 1950, 1954, 1955, 1961; cuid1734 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - McCauley [?], undated; cuid1735 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - McDonald, undated; cuid1736 (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - McDonald, JoAnn, undated; cuid1737 (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - McGinnis, Frank, undated; cuid1738 (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - McIlveen, Edward E., undated; cuid1739 (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - McKeen, John E., 1955; cuid1740 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - McLaughlin, Patricia A., 1999; cuid1741 (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - McLean, Noel, undated; cuid1742 (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - McNear, Cheryl, undated; cuid1743 (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - McShane, William, 1986; cuid1744 (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Mead, undated; cuid1745 (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Meglino, Bruce M., undated; cuid1746 (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Meinhold, Artie, 1942, 1950, 1955; cuid1747 (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Meinhold, Herbert, undated; cuid1748 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Meites, Lou, undated; cuid1749 (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Memon, Nasir, undated; cuid1750 (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Menashe, Louis, undated; cuid1751 (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - Mendik, undated; cuid1752 (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Mermelstein, David, 2002; cuid1753 (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Meskill, Thomas J., undated; cuid3613 (Box 5, Folder 186B)
  - Mesrobian, Robert B., 1955; cuid1754 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Messerschmitt, Richard, circa 1996; cuid1755 (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Messina, Philip, undated; cuid1756 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Meyer, Leonard S., undated; cuid1757 (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Meyers, Bernard L., undated; cuid1758 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Michels, Frank G., undated; cuid1759 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Middendorf, Henry Q., 1956, 1967, 1970; cuid1760 (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Midgette, Ernst L., 1954; cuid1761 (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Mijovic, Jovan, 1986; cuid1762 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Milas, Alfred, undated; cuid1763 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Milgram, Joseph B. Jr., undated; cuid1764 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Miller, Edward, undated; cuid1765 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Irving F., 1964; cuid1766 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miller, J., undated; cuid1767 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Wharton, undated; cuid1768 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Miller, William T., undated; cuid1769 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Millet, Marcus J., undated; cuid1770 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mishkin, E., undated; cuid1771 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mishuck, Eli, 1975; cuid1772 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Misra, Asoka, undated; cuid1773 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, William, undated; cuid1774 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mitra, Abhijit, undated; cuid3619 (Box 6, Folder 13B)
  - Mitnitsky, Samuel, undated; cuid1775 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Molof, Alan H., 1983; cuid1776 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mones, Arthur H., 1974; cuid1777 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Montclare, Jin, undated; cuid3620 (Box 6, Folder 16B)
  - Montrone, undated; cuid1778 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Moore, George E., 1964; cuid1779 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Robert J., 1941; cuid1780 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Morancie, Horace L., undated; cuid1781 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Morawetz, Herbert, 1978, 1981, 1995, 2001; cuid1782 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Morduchow, Morris, 1978; cuid1783 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Philip, 2001; cuid1784 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Morrison, Alexander W., undated; cuid1785 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Moslon, Julie, 1983; cuid1786 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Motzkin, Shirley, 1971, 1994; cuid1787 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Mow, William C. W., undated; cuid1788 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Moy, Kirsten S., undated; cuid1789 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, undated; cuid1790 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Mueller, Wheeler, 1978; cuid1791 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Mugglin, David, undated; cuid1792 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Mukherjee, Kalinath, 1971; cuid1793 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mukhopadhay, Sharmila M., undated; cuid1794 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mulcahy, David F., undated; cuid1795 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mulkin, undated; cuid1796 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Muller, F., undated; cuid1797 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Muller, S. H., undated; cuid1798 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Murawski, Thomas, 1973; cuid1799 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Murphy, Donald, undated; cuid1800 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Murray, 1954; cuid1801 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Murray, Robt T.K., undated; cuid1802 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Murray, R. William, 1994; cuid1803 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Muss, Jonathan, 1990s; cuid1804 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Myers, Robert J., undated; cuid1805 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Myerson, Allan, 1994; cuid1806 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- N
  - Nader, Ralph, undated; cuid1807 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Nadro, Edward Jr., undated; cuid1808 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Naevestad, Roy, undated; cuid1809 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Nagler, Stewart G., 1985, 1993, 2000; cuid1810 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Nagy, William, undated; cuid1811 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Nakahara, Tsuneo, 1994; cuid1812 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Napoli, Rudolph P., undated; cuid1813 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Naumovich, Gleb, undated; cuid1814 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Nelson, Ed, undated; cuid1815 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Nelson, Richard E., undated; cuid1816 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Nelson, Theodore W., circa 1978; cuid1817 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Nespoli, Paolo A., 1999; cuid1818 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Neugebauer, George H., undated; cuid1819 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Newman, Joseph H., undated; cuid1820 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Newstein, Maurice C., undated; cuid1821 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Newton, Harry, undated; cuid1822 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Nickelson, Stanley, 1973; cuid1823 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Nicks, Oran W., undated; cuid1824 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Nielsen, John P., 1985; cuid1825 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Nies, Nelson, 1938; cuid1826 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Nijhawan, Ramesh K., 1974; cuid1827 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Nisenson, Stan, undated; cuid1828 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Noetzel, undated; cuid1829 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Nomovetsky, Frederick, undated; cuid1830 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Nones, Allan S., undated; cuid1831 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Norton, Richard A., Col., undated; cuid1832 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Nourbakhsh, Said, 1986, 2000; cuid1833 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Novomestky, Frederick, undated; cuid1834 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Nowak, Theodore, undated; cuid1835 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Nulty, Thomas, undated; cuid1836 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Nummy, W.R., undated; cuid1837 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Nyquist, Ewald B., undated; cuid1838 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- O
  - Obeid, Diya, 2000; cuid1839 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Obermeyer, Charles, 1954; cuid1840 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - O'Connell. Liam P.F., circa 1974; cuid1841 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - O'Connor, Arthur M., 1956; cuid1842 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - O'Connor, John J., 1954, 1955; cuid1843 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - O'Dea, Tom, undated; cuid1844 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Oergel, Charles T., 1955; cuid1845 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Oguchi, Bunichi, circa 1996; cuid1846 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Okamoto, Yoshiyuki, undated; cuid1847 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - O'Leary, Hazel R., undated; cuid1848 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Oleck, John, undated; cuid1849 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Olexson, Gerard, circa 1974; cuid1850 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Oliner, Arthur A., 1967; cuid1851 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Olpin, A.R., undated; cuid1852 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Olsen, John C., circa 1937, 1952; cuid1853 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Olshan, Kenneth S., 1990s; cuid1854 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Omoagbi, Paul, undated; cuid1855 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Ooro, Otieno, undated; cuid1856 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Oppenheim, Alan and Rosa, circa 1998; cuid1857 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Orden, C.J., undated; cuid1858 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - O'Rourke, Kevin, undated; cuid1859 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Orso, Camillo A., circa 1997; cuid1860 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Osborne, undated; cuid1861 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Oster, Gerald, undated; cuid1862 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - Othmer, Donald, 1976; cuid1863 (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - Othmer, Mildred Topp, undated; cuid1864 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Otugen, M. Volkan, undated; cuid1865 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Oussani, James, undated; cuid1866 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Overberger, Charles G., 1952, 1955; cuid1867 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Overstreet, Jamahl W., undated; cuid1868 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Owades, Joseph L., 1999; cuid1869 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Owens, Major, 1999; cuid1870 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Oxman, Jack, undated; cuid1871 (Box 6, Folder 110)
- P
  - Pace, Norma, undated; cuid1872 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Pack, Arthur, undated; cuid1873 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Packard, David, undated; cuid1874 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Paczkowski, Henry C., undated; cuid1875 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Padavan, Frank, undated; cuid1876 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Padro, Dianne, undated; cuid1877 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Paige, Clifford E., undated; cuid1878 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Palchefsky, John, undated; cuid1879 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Pallo, Joseph S., undated; cuid1880 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Palmer, Charles, 1997; cuid1881 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Palocz, Istvan, circa 1987; cuid1882 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - Pannaparayil, Thomas, undated; cuid1883 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Panwar, Shivendra, 1986; cuid1884 (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - Panzer, Marvin, 1950; cuid1885 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - Papoulis, Athanasios, undated; cuid1886 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - Parandelis, Raina, undated; cuid1887 (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - Parikh, Mihir, undated; cuid1888 (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - Park, Lawrence, undated; cuid1889 (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - Parker, Jack R., undated; cuid1890 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - Parker, John C., undated; cuid1891 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Parry, John P., undated; cuid1892 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Parsons, Laura, undated; cuid1893 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Parsons, Richard D., undated; cuid1894 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Pascal, Donald D., 1973; cuid1895 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Patel, Rutton D., undated; cuid1896 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Patterson, Zahra, undated; cuid1897 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Pauling, Linus, undated; cuid1898 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Peale, Mundy I., 1963; cuid1899 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Pearce, Eli, 1974, 1986, 2000; cuid1900 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Pearlstein, Morton, undated; cuid1901 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Peck, Nicole, undated; cuid1902 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Penn, Lynn S., undated; cuid1903 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Penick, Joe E., undated; cuid1904 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Pennell, Knowlton E., circa 1955; cuid1905 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Penrose, Charles, undated; cuid1906 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Percy, undated; cuid1907 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Perez, John, undated; cuid1908 (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Perl, Martin, 1993, 1998; cuid1909 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Perric, Lawrence J., undated; cuid1910 (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Peshchansky, Vera, 1998; cuid1911 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Peterson, Beth, undated; cuid1912 (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Peterson, N., undated; cuid1913 (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Peterson, Roland, 1977; cuid1914 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Petit, Philippe, 1974, 1975; cuid1915 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Petrucci, S., undated; cuid1916 (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Phillips, Donald, 1986, 2000; cuid1917 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Pickel, Paul F., undated; cuid1918 (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Pierce, John Robinson, 1963; cuid1919 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Pierre, Charles, undated; cuid1920 (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Pighi, Louis H., 1979; cuid1921 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Pignataro, Louis, 1975, 1978; cuid1922 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Pillai, S. Unnikrishna, 1998; cuid1923 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Pinkert, Dorothy M., undated; cuid1924 (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Piore, Emanuel, 1967; cuid1925 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Pittle, Marvin S., undated; cuid1926 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Plympton, George W., circa 1900; cuid1927 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Poe, Alfred, undated; cuid1928 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Pollack, Myron I., undated; cuid1929 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Pomposello, Peter, undated; cuid1930 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Pond [Podnossoff], Jules, circa 1930; cuid1931 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Posner, N., 1986; cuid1932 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Post, Benjamin, undated; cuid1933 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Potts, Charles E., 1937, 1954; cuid1934 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Prassas, Elena, undated; cuid1935 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Pratt, Edmund T., Jr., undated; cuid1936 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Preiser, Stanley, 1969, 1975; cuid1937 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Prekeris, Algimantas, undated; cuid1938 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Press, Jack J., cuid1939 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Preston, Richard, circa 1998; cuid1940 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Prieto, Robert, circa 1999; cuid1941 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Prill, Stanley, 1963; cuid1942 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Privalsky, Chuck, circa 1968; cuid1943 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Prohaska, Dorothy, undated; cuid1944 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Proskauer, Eric S., 1978; cuid1945 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Protopapas, Angelos, undated; cuid1946 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Puccinelli, undated; cuid1947 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Puente, John, undated; cuid1948 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Purcell, Joe, undated; cuid1949 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Pyke, Geoffrey Nathaniel, undated; cuid1950 (Box 6, Folder 189)
- Q
  - Qian, Jinghua, undated; cuid1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Quaglino, James V., undated; cuid1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Queen, Nathaniel M., 1958; cuid1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - de Queiroz, Marcio S., undated; cuid1954 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Quinn, John, undated; cuid1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Quirin, Edward J., 1966; cuid1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- R
  - Rabins, Michael J., undated; cuid1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Racz, Ernest, undated; cuid1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Radden, Frank, undated; cuid1959 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rader, Charlies M., undated; cuid1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rader, Lloyd F., undated; cuid1961 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Radovic, undated; cuid1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ramberg, Eivind G.F., 1975; cuid1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ramo, Simon, undated; cuid1964 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rao, Bharat P., undated; cuid1965 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rasmussen, E. Hart, undated; cuid1966 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rassier, Donald, 1984; cuid1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ratay, Robert, undated; cuid1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Ratner, Bruce, 2001; cuid1969 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ratti, Umberto, undated; cuid1970 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Raymond, John H., Rev, circa 1871; cuid1971 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rechtschaffen, Bernard, circa 1983; cuid1972 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Reed, undated; cuid1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rees, R. [G.], undated; cuid1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Regna, Peter P., undated; cuid1975 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Reichle, Leonard F.C., undated; cuid1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reid, undated; cuid1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Reidy, Michael, 1986; cuid1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Reilly, Henry J., Gen., undated; cuid1979 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Reiser, Arnost, 1980s; cuid1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Reissner, Hans Jacob, undated; cuid1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Reitenbach, Nicholas, circa 1998; cuid1982 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Rennie, Richard, circa 1996; cuid1983 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Riccio, Anna Maria, 1975; cuid1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Richman, Jana, cuid1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Richmond, Martin R., undated; cuid1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Rickels, undated; cuid1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Riseborough, Peter S., undated; cuid1988 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Rittvo, Steve, undated; cuid1989 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Robbins, 1952; cuid1990 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Roberts, Arnie, 1976; cuid1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Roberts, Martin E., undated; cuid1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, Guner Suzek, undated; cuid1993 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., undated; cuid1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Roden, Martin S., undated; cuid1995 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Rodriguez, Josephine, circa 1996; cuid1996 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Roess, Roger, undated; cuid1997 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Youth, undated; cuid1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Portraits, 1947, 1952, 1955, 1957; cuid1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events 1940-1957, 1940-1968; cuid2000 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events undated, cuid2001 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Rogers, Joel, undated; cuid2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Rogers, [Warren] L., Rev., undated; cuid2003 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Rogge, Herbert, undated; cuid2004 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Romanelli, Otto C., 1990s; cuid2005 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Romano, Frank, 1978; cuid2006 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Ronald, Mark, cuid2007 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rorer, John, 1978; cuid2008 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rosen, Bernard, undated; cuid2009 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Rosenberry, Walter S., undated; cuid2010 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rosenthal, Myron, 1986; cuid2011 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, Saul W., 1955, 1967; cuid2012 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rosenthal, Seymour, undated; cuid2013 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rosenzweig, Carl, undated; cuid2014 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Ross, Gerald, undated; cuid2015 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ross, Ian, undated; cuid2016 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Ross, Keith, 2004; cuid2017 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Rossoff, undated; cuid2018 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Roth, George Col., 1933; cuid2019 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Rothbard, Murray, undated; cuid2020 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Rothschild, Fred, undated; cuid2021 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rothschild, Walter N., Jr., undated; cuid2022 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rowley, Louis N., Jr., 1976, 1968, 1978; cuid2023 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Roy, Dipak, undated; cuid2024 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ruben, Samuel, 1979; cuid2025 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Rubenstein, Charlie, undated; cuid2026 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Rubin, cuid2027 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Rudin, Paul, undated; cuid2028 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Ruppel, Alfred E., circa 1975; cuid2029 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Russell, Edward, 1954, 1972; cuid2030 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Russell, Joan, 1983; cuid2031 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Russell, Jules, circa 1954; cuid2032 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Russell, William M., cuid2033 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Russo, Onofrio "Nick", circa 1998; cuid2034 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Ruten, William H., undated; cuid2035 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Ryan, Albert J., Lt. Col., 1954-1955; cuid2036 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Ryan, John F., 1931; cuid2037 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- S
  - Sabavala, Darius, undated; cuid2038 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Sabet, M., undated; cuid2039 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Sacher, Alex, undated; cuid2040 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Sack, Edgar A., undated; cuid2041 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Saidla, Leo E.A., 1952; cuid2042 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Sakai, Wataru, undated; cuid2043 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Salkind, Alvin J., undated; cuid2044 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Saltman, Bethany, undated; cuid2045 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Salzinger, Kurt, 1982, 1985; cuid2046 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Sanator, Robert J., 1980, 1984; cuid2047 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sannizjari, Salvatore, undated; cuid2048 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Sarno, Frank J., undated; cuid2049 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Savitt, Sidney A., 1983, 1985; cuid2050 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Sawyer, 1951; cuid2051 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Sawyer, Fred, undated; cuid2052 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Sbasching, Richard W., 2001; cuid2053 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Sbordone, George J., undated; cuid2054 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Schaaf, undated; cuid2055 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Schachter, 1986; cuid2056 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Schaefer, John P., undated; cuid2057 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Schaffer, Bernard, undated; cuid3609 (Box 7, Folder 107B)
  - Schaffner, Charles E., 1955; cuid2058 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Schallcross, Lewis, undated; cuid2059 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Schatter, Arnie, undated; cuid2060 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Schein, Eugene, undated; cuid2061 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Scheiner, Lowell, undated; cuid2062 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Scher, Seymour, 1982; cuid2063 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Schilling, Ronald, undated; cuid2064 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Schillinger, A. George, undated; cuid2065 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Schlect, Matt, undated; cuid2066 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Schleher, Daniel Curtis, undated; cuid2067 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Schleich, Donald, 1986; cuid2068 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Schleuning, Herbert W., undated; cuid2069 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Schmidling, David, undated; cuid2070 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Schmidt, Harry, undated; cuid2071 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Schmidt, Jeanette, undated; cuid2072 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Schoenhaar, Roy C., 1971; cuid3610 (Box 7, Folder 122B)
  - Schroeder, Robert W., undated; cuid2073 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Schuck, O. Hugo, undated; cuid2074 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Schuck, Robert E., 1970; cuid2075 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Schurig, W. Fred, undated; cuid2076 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Schuler, Raymond T., undated; cuid2077 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Schuster, Seymour, undated; cuid2078 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Schwalb, Allen J., 1995; cuid2079 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Schwalm, William H., undated; cuid2080 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Schwartz, Jerome, undated; cuid2081 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Scicutella, John, undated; cuid2082 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Scott, C.F., undated; cuid2083 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Scott, Shannon, undated; cuid2084 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Seidenberg, Ivan, undated; cuid2085 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Sekimoto, Tadahiro, 1998; cuid2086 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Selby, Harold E., 1960; cuid2087 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Selesnick, Ivan, undated; cuid2088 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Senitzky, Benjamin, undated; cuid2089 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Sepahbin, Amir H., undated; cuid2090 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Setterstrom, Carl A., undated; cuid2091 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Settle, Sandy, undated; cuid2092 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Severance, Dennis, cuid2093 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Sforza, Pasquale, 1993; cuid2094 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Shah, Chandni, undated; cuid2095 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Shamis, Sidney S., undated; cuid2096 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Shang, Joseph S., undated; cuid2097 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Shapiro, Lawrence, undated; cuid2098 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Shavers, Sgt., undated; cuid2099 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Shaw, Leonard, 1986, 1994; cuid2100 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Sheldon, Rufus, undated; cuid2101 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Sheldon, Samuel, undated; cuid2102 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Shepherd, Donald S., 1980; cuid2103 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Sheverev, Valery, undated; cuid2104 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Shields, B.A., undated; cuid2105 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Shinn, Richard R, undated; cuid2106 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Shmoys, Jerry, 1967; cuid2107 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Shnidman, Yitzahak, undated; cuid2108 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Shooman, Martin, 1974, 1998; cuid2109 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Shultis, Christine, circa 1996; cuid2110 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Shustek, Leonard, 1997-1998; cuid2111 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Sibner, Leslie, undated; cuid2112 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Siderer, Jack, undated; cuid2113 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Sie, John J., circa 1996; cuid2114 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Silber, Leo M., undated; cuid2115 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Sill, Joshua Woodrow (1831-1862), undated; cuid2116 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Silleck, Clarence F., 1963, 1983, 1985; cuid2117 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Silver, Sheldon, undated; cuid2118 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Simanca, Santiago, undated; cuid2119 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Simins, Herbert J., 1977; cuid2120 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Simmonds, G., undated; cuid2121 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Simo, Constance, undated; cuid2122 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Simpson, Murray, cuid3611 (Box 8, Folder 4C)
  - Singer, Gerald, 1968; cuid2123 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Singer, Henry, 1994; cuid2124 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Singer, Joel, undated; cuid2125 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sipress, Jack, circa 1995; cuid2126 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sirota, Julius, undated; cuid2127 (Box 8, Folder 9)